overlandagency.com 2007-12-10

# Overland Agency | Interactive Advertising Agency - About - Contact Us - Privacy Policy

**Overland Agency's Privacy Policy**

Your privacy is very important to us. We do not sell or otherwise provide your personal information to third parties for any reason, except as required by law. Please read this privacy policy to learn more about the ways in which we use and protect your personal information. 

In this Privacy Policy we provide detailed information on when and why we collect your personal information, how we use it, and how we keep it secure. 

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

In general, you can browse our website without giving us any personal information. We use web-tracking software to analyze traffic to this website in order to understand our customers and visitors needs and to continually improve our site for them. This web tracking software collects only anonymous, aggregate statistics. 

However, certain activities on our site require you to provide personal information. For example you need to register to read whitepapers and sign up for events. As part of the registration process, we ask you to create an account by providing your name, title, phone number, e-mail address, and mailing address. 

  * During the registration process, if you request to be contacted by Overland Agency when new resources are available, we will use the information to send you e-mail or mail when new whitepapers, articles, news or seminars are available. You can unsubscribe at any time.
  * During the registration process, if you selected to not be contacted or notified of new resources, or if you later unsubscribed we will respect your privacy. 

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We do not sell or otherwise provide your personal information to third parties for any reason, except as required by law. 

**Children and Privacy**

Our website does not offer information intended to attract children. Overland Agency does not knowingly solicit personal information from children under the age of 13.

 **Security of Personal Information**

When you submit any form on overlandagency.com, we use a secure server. The secure server software (SSL) helps protect your information as it travels over the Internet by encrypting that information before it is sent to us. We have also implemented industry-standard security mechanisms and procedures to protect data from loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

 **Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file containing information that a website transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies allow us to provide a user-friendly registration and log-in process. A cookie can not give us access to your computer or to information beyond what you provide to us. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies; consult your browser's manual or online help if you want information on restricting or disabling the browser's handling of cookies. If you disable cookies, you can still view the publicly available information on our website, but you will not be able to take advantage of offers or activities requiring registration.

 **Links to Other Websites**

Our website contains links to information on other websites. We do not have any control over these other websites, and therefore we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information that you provide while visiting those sites. Those sites are not governed by this Privacy Policy, and if you have questions about how a site uses your information, consult that site's privacy statement.

 **Unsubscribing or Changing Your Account Information**

If you have registered with Overland Agency, you may change your preferences or unsubscribe at any time by following the instructions provided here.

 **Your Consent**

By using our website, you consent to the collection and use of the information you provide to us as outlined in this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time and without notice. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will publish those changes on this page. If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Phone: 503-963-8501

Fax: 503-963-8502

117 SW Taylor Suite 300

Portland, OR 97204

This document was last updated June 2007.
